Hello friends, welcome to Policy
Terms. Today we will discuss dental health
insurance policies. You often
ask whether a dental health
insurance policy is available. The
answer is that no stand-
alone or dedicated dental health insurance
policy is currently available. Although dental treatment is available in case of accidental injury
under your normal health insurance policy,
it is
limited to maintaining your tooth alignment or normal functioning. It does not cover any dental fillings or
RCTs.
Furthermore, some high-end policies,
which have very high premiums, provide limited
outpatient treatment.
This limited outpatient treatment may cover some dental
treatments, including basic dental treatments
like fillings and other dental procedures.
Furthermore, some corporates purchase
a group medical insurance policy for their employees, which may
cover dental treatments. It may also cover all pre-
assisting or any other general dental
requirement, including dental fillings
or any other dental procedures.  Treatment can be covered
if the group or corporate has
purchased such a policy for its employees.
Apart from all this, friends, as I have
already told you, no dedicated dental
insurance policy
is available. Apart from this, if you have any question,
please ask in the comment and if you
liked the video, then definitely subscribe to the channel.